that doesn't seem
good last week we turned
$437 into $3,000 the account is
currently sitting at
$3,000 [__] dollar now the goal was
to turn 400 to800 but we actually ended
up setting forget more than we should
have on the trade and we got a really
nice second entry in it we are currently
obviously close position you guys can
see right here that the account is at
officially $3,000 you guys can see here
on my effect book and the goal was $800
but it ended up playing better in our
favorite we almost blew the account
right at the beginning the account is
not looking that good right now you guys
can see that we are currently down about
$32 on the accounts but ended up playing
out in our favorite now this week's goal
is to turn $3,000 into $6,000 so let's
see how it goes
all right guys it is Sunday evening so
it is the first day of The Challenge on
week number three first day with the new
haircut on the new channel for the week
first of all what is going on in here
this the
cat's yeah she's shy she's camera shy
she had a party here last night and she
[__] went crazy but this is week
three we're taking $100 to a maill we
took last week
$437 to $3,000 and now this week the go
to take $33,000 to $6,000 ,000 just to
show you guys like always it's currently
Sunday evening 8:00 the account is
currently sitting at $3,000 let me show
you guys the market for this week
because honestly I think it's as good as
they were last week so you guys know
every single week in the market is
different some weeks have better
opportunities than others but I do see
great opportunity in this week so let me
show you so the first one is going to be
Euro USD you guys can see we have a very
clear left head right shoulder and now
we are retesting the neckline of The
Head and Shoulders retesting the EMA and
then we have a 4-Hour bearish engulfing
Candlestick now if you guys saw last
week's Series this exact same pattern
would look extremely familiar from the
trade that took us from $437 at $3,000
let me actually show you guys what time
is
it right now in Miami 7:37 in the
afternoon refreshing the web page so
this is last week's trade that made us
about about
$22,000 it's going to be this market
right here so you guys can see USD JPY
we got this left head right shoulder
retested the neckline retested the EMA
trade boom dropped one to was actually
more a 1 to six to was around a 1 to six
R to reward now for this one what does
this market look like exactly the same
Big Head and Shoulders retest to the
neckline rejection from the EMA and then
engulfing cesti so we're going to enter
this trade as soon as we get a body
cesti closure under this that is for
Euro USD you guys can see it right here
EUR USD next is going to be USD CHF so
USD CHF on The Daily time frame we are
clearly bearish heading to the downside
now I'm simply waiting for price to have
a pullback into around this area of
Interest potentially round psychological
level
8900 when you go down to the 4our I want
it to come back in and then and retest
this EMA level right here retest that
EMA level it's going to confirm to
reject this previous structure Point
level right here and then we're going to
be able to head to the downside very
very very nice trade next is going to be
GBP CAD so GBP CAD currently on the
weekly time frame we've had very slow
down one two weeks at a strong round
psychological level
1775 and then the daily time frame you
can see how from this bll run it was
very strong right it was you know 2 days
pause one strong push 2 days pause 3
four 5 days of very strong push but then
it's been here for about two weeks in
the same spot so it's literally showing
signs of slowing down so this gives us
an opportunity to enter a counter Trend
trade now you can see right here on the
4H hour time frame we are literally
lining up a left head and then a right
shoulder to where this Market we can
then have a break a retest to then sell
to the down downside and then retest
this neckline of the EMA we are
literally lining up the same exact thing
as EUR USD it is the same exact thing
the only thing is that EUR USD is about
two to 3 days ahead of it let me show
you guys this is EUR USD right now
currently in the 4 Hour very clear left
head right shoulder break and then
retest when you go to GBP CAD GBP CAD we
are still missing the break and then the
retest so your USD we already have this
push and we already have this retest
which is very clear to observe here the
break and then the retest it's exactly
we're waiting for on GBP CAD in order to
enter this trade and then last but not
least it's going to be the famous the
degeneracy degener degeneracy degeneracy
say it with me
degener I can't even
say [__] degeneracy right of
gbpjpy so GBP JPY we have a ginormous
left head and then a
potential right shoulder again key
potential because it has not happened
yet so I'm going to wait for this price
to have a pullback into this level to
then sell it'll retest this strong level
of resistance how is done in the past to
that sell and then we would retest the
EMA which is then dip into it so then
head to the downside now why do I say
degener
huh because we can have a counter Trend
trade what does this mean this means
that we are at a support level whenever
we're here we reject above whenever we
are under we reject to the downside well
now we're Above So now this can have a
push to the upside to create that right
shoulder to then have the cell to the
downside so we can be degenerates and
catch this trade as a buy right here up
into this point right here and then we
can catch the cell once it creates that
right shoulder from here back down in to
this level now this is Ultimate
degenerator right degenerator de D gen
[__] D gen [__] you know so I don't
recommend it but the opportunity is
there so this would be our first dgen
trade which would be counter Trend trade
up into this area of interest to then
sell and then the real trade would then
be the sell once we're up at this level
so yeah that's pretty much it honestly
look like a fun week
this week trading it is
currently 8:00 p.m. that whole
explanation took me 5 minutes does medit
trator still have the money in it still
has the money in
it doesn't matter so tonight's what what
should we do tonight Sunday I think we
should just chill right I mean your
definition of chill is very different
I'm honestly scared of your definition
of chill cuz your definition of chill is
a chance of us doing nothing at the
house or us stranding in the highway cuz
something by the way let me let me
actually show you guys this so this is
for my students but I I give these away
all the time so I have set forget
pendants that I give away literally all
the time like he's wearing one right now
I have a couple so I have like literally
a [__] ton of these things that
literally just sitting here I need a
reason to give these away
now L have [__] they're all brand new I
don't know all I have to say is
subscribe then maybe you can wi have a
shi of them just sitting here see you
guys
later all right guys so market update it
is currently 9:43 in the
morning it's your fault market update
before I show you guys what just
happened it is currently 9:43 in the
morning as you guys can see the count is
currently sadly still sitting exactly
the same as
$3,000 why well because I fell asleep
last night can't even lie I missed the
TR I fell asleep last night look at this
[__] right here bro so Euro USD you guys
can see exactly how I mentioned left
head right shoulder retest of the
neckline I was waiting to enter as soon
as we would have a break under this
right here and boom the trade completely
went straight to my takeprofit the
fastest one to two about literally the
whole entire challenge this could have
easily taken our account from $3,000 to
$6,000 like that but I was sleeping so
look this is right now on the 4H hour if
I would go down to then the 1 hour you
can see how I have this line right here
and my prediction was for price to break
under it and then retest it to then sell
price never retested it but you guys can
see here at the time that that happened
so this Candlestick right there follow
this line all the way down here you can
see how down here it's literally 3 in
the morning so if we follow this line up
you can see how it's that Candlestick
right there July
29th 2024 3 in the
morning 3 in the morning last night I
was knocked out just to show you guys
I'm a a man of uh my word this [__]
tracks it for me the [__] whoop potato
potato so you guys can see here last
night I knocked out so I got 76%
recovery last night I knocked out at
1:00 in the morning woke up 8:47 so I
was like right in the middle of my sleep
last night so wasn't able to catch this
trade it is what it is next is going to
be USD CHF USD CHF our prediction is for
price to make it up into around this
area so then we sell so we're actually
actively pulling back to that area right
now so this is actively going to
probably be a trade very very soon we
just have to wait for price to have our
bearish engulfing so I'll probably enter
this trade when we have have something
like this so as soon as price has a
little quick break and retest from this
price right here I'll be interested in
taking this trade next is GBP CAD so GBP
CAD currently on the 4our we are looking
like we're creating that left head and
that right shoulder well we definitely
are but I can't sell right into this
support level CU if I were to sell right
into this support level something like
this would happen that then we have a
reaction to the upside so the only way
that I would I actually enter this trade
is if break retest and then enter the
cell in this market right now I am not
interested in executing this trade at
this High especially if the daily time
frame is closing with a strong rejection
Wick like this even though we still have
7 hours for this daily Candlestick to
close you know I I can't enter this
trade just yet I would have to wait for
a strong daily body stick to close under
the retest and then the sell next is
going to be GBP JPY so we were
interested in taking these counter Trend
trades again fell asleep last night
wasn't interested in taking it but it is
looking quite interesting depending if
today closes like this so once again if
this daily Candlestick in about 7 hours
closes like this as a dogee then for
tonight in London session I will then be
interested in executing this trade
potentially when it would have some type
of break and retest here to then head to
the upside but for now not really
interested I have to wait for this daily
time frame to then close so I can
actually determine what I'm going to do
CU if it does close like this then it's
going to give us the indication that it
will come up into this level to then
give us that left head and then the
right shoulder so then we could catch
those counter Trend trade buys and then
usdcad currently we are at the high of
the market and then I am going to be
waiting for price to just break and R
this under it's pretty much done nothing
so the closest one to execution I would
say is USD CHF
and uh probably yeah USD CHF and
probably GJ so obviously we missed Euro
USD so the trade already played out I am
literally no longer interested in
nothing come us Euro USD the trade
played out it happened it's gone so
sucks that would have been a really good
start to the week we would have probably
already been at at the goal but that
just shows you guys that the strategy is
consistently giving you great
opportunities in the market you just
have to be ready to catch them I you
know I wasn't up and honestly probably a
year ago I'd be beating myself up for it
and I would stay up all night tonight
but now it's like bro I'm ahead uh I'm
ahead of the challenge two weeks so I
don't really care if I miss a trade it's
not a big deal so this just confirms to
me that the next year I'm going to take
is going to be a very high probability
trade because the set fre strategy once
again is showing you guys the potential
that it has to give you a high
probability trade of going in One
Direction versus that so right now it is
currently 94 48 we're probably just
going to wait on USD CHF which is the
main pair probably hit the gym probably
pick up Jordan oh by the way I saw you
guys like Jordan in the last video bro
my ass my ass feels cold as [__] so
we're going to bring him back we're
going to talk tell him to talk more
about his story and kind of how he plans
to recover from everything he has he's
set a crazy goal for himself and I want
him to share that so you guys will see
more of that throughout the video but
just to pretty much summarize everything
USD CHF and GJ we'll update you guys
throughout the day all right guys so
trade update we're about we're about to
leave right now cuz they suspend my
license notice of order of suspension of
your license so yeah for those of you
guys that ask I don't know how you have
a license I don't all right I drift I
[__] race and it's just spend my
license have to go to court now and get
it back but I love it it's fun and then
like now without a license we're going
to go do men [__] to go get our license
back all right so this is right now
currently USD CHF you can see it's the 1
hour time frame on USD CHF so we're just
going to wait for this break and retest
as of right now it just keeps pushing up
to that area of Interest which is good
it's exactly what we want we want price
to hit that EMA and then reject and then
retest USD CHF it just absolutely
beautiful trade pretty much I cannot get
any better than that gvp CAD still
waiting for this and then GBP
JPY we are going to wait for this later
it is currently 10:32 in the morning so
literally about an hour later from the
last update let's go get our license
back this line is for appointment only
if you don't have an appointment please
get on the other side do it do it do
it oh I can't eat yeah I can't eat I'm
on a I'm on a fast so right now I'm
actually on a 30
probably like 32 hour fast tomorrow is
going to be 48 then I'm done longest
fast I've ever done usually I do it when
I start getting too bloated trying to
get shredded out here you know what I'm
saying uh trade update is currently
10:00 at night me actually take you guys
with have you guys seen my F1 car so I
have a F1 Sim let me actually show you
guys my F1 Sim so this is actually my F1
Sim so my goal was to actually wrap it
like the color of one of my cars but it
came red and I feel like it pops good on
the wall because there's nothing red
through about the whole house they have
like the Harley Harley's Blue and then
the set and forget sign is blue I don't
think they've ever seen the Harley
either no there's in the Harley this
should even turn
on got time for this [__] trade update
all right so trade update I actually
update you guys on on the trade where it
is right now so again it is currently
10:00 at night let me actually do it
here on the computer is how I used to do
before so I search up what time is it
right now in Miami this is the last time
that I actually refreshed it I refresh
it now
9:59 p.m. so the markets Euro USD so let
me show you guys the First Market it's
going to be Euro USD so as you guys can
see our trade from earlier would have
played out absolutely beautiful trade
gone so I and forget this is the next
trade which I am going to stay up
tonight to then enter usdchf having the
pull back to the area of Interest
exactly how I wanted to the 4H hour time
frame very slow down at this area which
is exactly what we wanted to see and
then the 30 minute time frame we are
going to be waiting for a little quick
break retest of this area to then go to
the downside GBP CAD is literally doing
nothing what we wanted to do so
currently we are at the high still we
are rejecting and in the 4-Hour time
frame we want for price to obviously
break and retest under to then sell it's
not doing what we want to not really
that interested GJ is having the stop at
this area exactly how we want to daily
time frame has given us a daily bullish
pinbar which is what we want to then
take the counter Trend trade by so if I
go down to the end the 1 hour we can see
that the 1 hour is kind of accumulating
at this area the only way I would
actually enter this trade is if it were
to give me a bullish engulfing
Candlestick on this 30 minute time frame
so if I have a Candlestick like this
I'll probably enter right after that
Candlestick stop loss right around here
that'll give me about a 1 to 2 to 7 rist
to reward so 1 to 2 to 7 should be very
very solid and it'll be the perfect
counter Trend trick so we're waiting on
that so what I like to do is I put an
alarm above this area right here so I
just set an alarm right around here so
if price does break above that I will be
notified and then lastly USD CAD which
we are at the high waiting for the break
and bries under honestly I'm not even
interested in this trade just has so
much more so yeah basically sum it up GJ
we can probably enter tonight on the 30
minute time frame once we have that
break and retest from this level and
then USD CHF break and re the under just
to show you guys currently the account
is still sitting at
$3,774 just set and for game so let's
see what time London we end up entering
the trade tonight a bro I feel like
[__] [__] I got to eat we should make
it more interesting when you win a trade
you should eat no no no no no no people
want to see the trades I get
big no hell no got me [__] I'm going
to look like you you all right guys
straight update we had a little
inconvenience one of our doors got
locked last night we're trying to unlock
it with this for those you guys that
don't know I am not the best handyman so
this was pretty much useless currently
we have a very interesting morning right
now it is currently 9:24 in the morning
as you guys can see here 9:24 in the
morning on Tuesday Morning 9:24 so last
night once again fell
asleep sorry [__] fa again dude now
you want to know what this whole fast
[__] literally like ass but I dropped 8
lb in 2 days not eating so I show you
how much water we'd have I was at 194
and now I'm at 18 like 6 185 market
update So currently right now on USD CHF
literally exactly how I've been
explaining yo yo yo yo yo I I got to I
got to [__] put me on Wall Street cuz
put me on Wall Street bro cuz this is
[__] getting crazy I'm predicting
every single one of these [__] moves
look at this yes yesterday we had the
pull back exactly to the area of
Interest exactly how I wanted and then I
literally told you guys on the 30 minute
time frame we were at this point right
here I'm like all right we got to wait
for this quick break and retest
structure to them sell cuz that was the
last higher low structure level then as
we continue to create new higher highs
and higher lows then this higher low
structure level pretty much becomes
irrelevant the next breaking retest
structure we want to get is from this
point right here literally just
following the structure and we have the
market like this this is literally the
last higher low structure point so we
have to wait for a break and retest here
but if the market does this well then
this becomes a new higher low so then we
this becomes irrelevant and we have to
wait for a break and retest structure
Level under here I hope this makes sense
I'm I'm pretty much like teaching you
guys live right now right this is what I
do every single Sunday with my students
when I teach them the strategy but
coming back into here if I just pretty
much remove the replay you guys can
clearly see that then this became the
the new higher low this box right here
is now irrelevant so now this is the new
higher low where we have to wait for the
break and retest and that is exactly
what we have done we have had a
beautiful rejection from the area of
Interest exactly how I explained then we
had the retest and now we have the
engulfing so I'm looking to enter this
trade probably in the next 2 minutes and
38 seconds as soon as this candle to
closes because we have a beautiful left
head right shoulder retest the engulfing
I'll have my entry right on here stop
loss right around here where I should
have entered this trade is up here and I
should be up about 11 Pips in profit but
it is what it is you guys hear the
Discord those are the students is going
crazy right now like they're
[Applause]
[__] so basically I'm looking to
enter this trade in the next minutes and
58 seconds so we're going to come back
to it in just a second so this is where
I'm looking to enter this trade if it
keeps going down look at this if it
keeps going down that's where I just
placed it like a minute to go so if it
keeps going down I have to wait for a
little we pullback whatever next GBP JPY
so go watch yesterday's literally watch
like go back like 15 [__] seconds
look at this GBP JPY yesterday I told
you guys if this Body candles s closed
above this one I would then buy so I had
my thing there boom look at that I would
have quickly caught in a easy one to 1.4
on this trade so I predicted the
direction of this Market to Perfection
literally exactly how I explained the
last night because we had this break of
the Candlestick stay here with the
charts so we had this break of the
Candlestick and obviously if you guys
see the time of when that happened that
happened around 1: in the morning down
here you guys can see it was literally
as soon as the market was entering
London session I fell asleep so this is
exactly what happened this morning price
started having pullback now a lot of you
guys are going to be asking me why
didn't you enter now here again well
because there's no confirmation to enter
here there's a confirmation to enter at
that point but now this is having a very
strong pullback and I'm not that
interested in entering the trade even
though if I were to have been in this
trade from this point right here I would
be obviously set and forgetting but I
don't want to now enter a trade without
a confirmation so this would have been
the trade that I took I can't retake
this trade right here with no
confirmation so basically I'm saving
myself from a potential loss on GBP JPY
but I am still very interested in
entering a trade here if we have a
rejection from this point so we have a
rejection like this dogee right here and
then we have a bullish engulfing like
this one if we have literally these same
three candlesticks but right here I will
enter this trade 100% so USD CHF closing
in about in the next 30
seconds oh no it closed oh [__] all
right so we're going to enter this trade
in the next five minutes so you never
want to enter a trade as as soon as it
closes because usually like the first
minute or two it's creating the wick to
the upside so it's creating that Wick
that Wick that Wick that Wick and that's
where you can get a better entry so if
you just see right now price is having
that pullback and I believe it can
easily have a pullback to about I think
have a pullback to around like this
structure point right here so it's
literally on its way there already I've
saved probably about two three Pips
which is spread but we're going to
literally enter this trade right now
just to show you guys it is currently
9:30 in the morning
we don't have any trads right now on the
account let me show you guys the my
effects book my effect book so you guys
can see that my effect book currently
exactly the same no trades right now and
then this is the history of all the
trades we've taken on the account so I
don't forget all right guys so market
update it is currently
9:49 in the morning we are officially in
the trade so I literally enter let me
before that let me show you guys the
time right so what time is it right now
in Miami I come over here I refresh the
website 9:49 in the morning so literally
to show you guys we just entered the
trade so look pull up here so you guys
remember how I literally just mentioned
that we were going to have a pull back
into this level to then sell so we
literally had that pull back perfectly I
went exactly to where I I didn't go
exactly to where I anticipated but got
really close I entered it and just to
show you guys proof I was just recording
for Instagram right now as soon as we
entered the trade we're literally like
using margin and [__] because we entered
the trade pretty much risked everything
so I just wanted to show you guys that
but now we're officially in the trade we
are up $400 on it currently right now
like always have to show you guys that
it is a real account so you guys can see
right here that it is indeed a real
account you guys can see where the
account is currently sitting and we're
currently now going to just wait but I
explained to you guys perfectly this I
explained to you guys the break and
retest here I entered at this next
retest where we should have waited for
it here should have waited for the break
and retest here to then sell s but then
this didn't happen here but it did
happen here we then entered after the
engulfing which ideally we should be
entering up here but we didn't get that
and then GBP JPY currently it literally
stopped right at that area where we
would have entered yesterday and I would
have loved to be in this because I like
this better cuz it's a degenerate trade
it's the counter Trend trade and I do
believe on The Daily time frame this is
going to have the overall push to the
this level if you notice the daily Wick
has pretty much made it about 60% of the
weight so we're almost there but USD CHF
just looks more of a a less degenerate
type of trade if this daily time frame
closes anything like this or even it's
daily time frame closes above this right
here I'm just going to say this right
now if the daily time frame closes above
that line right there we're we're good
we're good we're going to turn into
about like $7,000 by this week 4H hour
looks very good as well 4our time frame
looks very solid believe it or not I
don't love that engulfing Candlestick I
don't love it because it's aabu so it
does have the opportunity to come back
and create that Wick but I do love this
1 hour Head and Shoulders pattern and
this 1 hour very strong bearish
Candlestick so this candle closes in
about 7 minutes so let's see how it
closes then so
set that doesn't seem good
thought you said you were a
wizard it's all your fault yo we might
blow this [__] right now bro no no no no
and you know what's funny I was so hyped
bro I woke up like I was this [__] man I
I what did I say ear like 10 minutes ago
um put me on Wall
Street was stre heard you all right so
in normal people terms what's going on
so basically obviously I'm risking 100%
of the account to then flip very fast so
it looks like the trade is having a
pullback to then retest that structure
point I mean it's literally exactly what
I said earlier earlier I said it's going
to have that pullback to create that
wick on top of that Candlestick but if
it does go that far we'll probably have
a mark Mar c and then the trade would
probably close there's no other way of
getting any more transparent with this I
am literally showing you guys the should
we just lie to people bro what if we
just never make it happen and then we
deposit another three and then we buy
yes so then we're not wrong or should we
wait cuz it could go back into profit wa
we [__] hold boys we we set and
forget we're going to huddle so yeah
basically right now currently we are
1300 and loss so we'll update you guys
in 15 minutes yo how's the trade going
TR
update what are you doing this is this
is going to make sense don't worry about
this Che up is looking all right you
guys can see currently we are now
rejecting this point right here it's
like I said it's going to come back
reject that EMA and then potentially
obviously reject down you guys can see
right here on the account that we are
currently pretty much at break even 1
hour time frame looks pretty good see
we're literally about 100 bucks 1 hour
time from looks pretty good and then
we're just waiting now on this 4H hour
Candlestick to close if it closes like
look so what I meant by that is that
that Candlestick did not have a wick to
the upside so what I said is that price
is going to have to pull all the way
back up create that Wick to then head to
the downside that is exactly what the
[__] it did it went up created that Wick
and now it's actually having the
rejection so you know we're still not
fully in the green you know we're still
around a little bit of draw down but
definitely in a much better position
that we were in earlier so currently
right now market update it is 11 no
12:15 in the afternoon so about 2 hours
later from the last update we probably
won't see much movement now cuz you know
Market slows down now towards the ending
of the day so we're probably going to go
ahead to gym I'm going to eat right now
for the first time in 2 days 48 hour
fast I am not doing this again my head
hurts I feel like ass so we'll probably
eat an after after I eat probably going
to go see the Rolls-Royce I haven't seen
it in a while it's still broken and um
let's just see where the day takes us so
I just want to show you guys how legit
and how transparent this is we are up
right now
$2,400 oh man and all we did was
literally set and forget so the trade
came back into here I explained that it
was going to hold and then we push the
trade down so I just woke up from a nap
I go to my phone and I look at my phone
and it's literally blowing going up by
dude I think it's easily over 10,000
people every single day just catching
this USD CHF trailer you can literally
see everybody here making money cuz I'm
posting this on my story look this guy
was up a couple hundred bucks this guy
is up
$4,000 bro look at this look at this you
cannot make this up I'm literally
showing you guys how transparent and how
legit I do it every single day and it's
not just me catching it it's literally
tens of thousands of people catching it
every single day all right guys so I'm
holding the camera right now SE have to
go to a doctor's appointment or
something so
literally I'm just laughing because I am
so transparent and so legit I'm going to
show you in a second how many people
actually entered this trade so I just
recorded that before I'm about to show
you what I'm going to show you guys
right now boys we are up currently
$22,000 on the trade it is $142 in the
afternoon as you can see in that top
right corner all we have done is [__]
set and forget literally this is all we
have done [__] set and forget you
guys probably can't see that [__] but
the point is we just set and forget let
me show you so earlier we were up here
in draw down and then we were simply set
and forgetting and now the price has
haded the push to the downside the wick
I have explained it perfectly everything
has happened to the tea exactly how I
have explained beautiful full massive 4H
hour bearish Eng golfing Candlestick
what we are waiting for right now is to
see if this daily Candlestick in 3 hours
is going to close under this line or not
so we have to wait for that to happen in
order for us to be determining if we're
going to continue to hold this trade
because we're literally at the profit
for the week so the profit for the week
is literally $6,000 and we're currently
up right almost at that point so for now
Now set and forget we broke a little
sweat earlier but we managed to hold GBP
JPY we did not enter this trade one
because USD CHF looked a lot cleaner and
honestly if I would have entered this
trade if USD CHF did not look as clean
as this I would have taken this rather
than USD CHF and I would have probably
blown the account so I avoided a loss to
Perfection on GBP JPY so for now USD CHF
just set and forget and if at this point
in the video you are not subscribed to
the channel hit that [__] subscribe
button we're dropping a video like this
every single week until I turn $100 into
a million subscribe put the notification
Bell cuz you do not want to miss this
[__] look my phone's raring up people
want to catch these traits all right so
I know this shit's loud but so we got
Sensei a gift for his birthday funny
enough me and Sensei actually have the
same birthday I bought this right for
his birthday and I've had it for like 2
weeks and I haven't even gave it to him
so we're going to go drop it off now
lives like 2 hous down for me and then
we're going to go hit the gym we are
currently let it load $2,200 in profit
it's pretty much how much we're up so
let's go drop off this gift hit the gym
and then probably see Jordan
later hello hey sir did just hey for
you open be the story behind this
Fu up the
gift there's a story behind this gift
it's going to make a lot of sense once
you open it I if you know you know only
if you know you
know yes
sir but so this is a very special
edition watch so this is a Muhammad Ali
M Blanc watch so you see it has like Ali
through here and then you see the
Muhammad Ali everywhere throughout here
the mham Ali
everywhere they only did seven out of 15
in the whole
world for the non pen lovers out there
how much was that
pen the not pen lovers out there that
was a Mont Blanc Mont Blanc pens average
of like 500 to like two grand more or
less but when it's a special edition
Muhammad
Ali uh 15 in the world only one drop the
prices tends to be a bit more than that
so how much was it let's just say it's
just Rich [__] [__] you know
Rich [__] [__] would understand
I have two month Blan pens and you want
to know what's funny I've never used
them in my life it's more of like a if
you know you know but honestly since
I've never used it you really never know
all right so this is how you drift the
Ferrari right so look right now it's in
race mode you got to put it over here
turn off the track
blow it look back make sure no cop if
there's a cop it doesn't
matter
[Music]
[__] let me see the let me see the wash
cuz if it doesn't have diamonds I don't
I Chester legs clip a coin you want
heads or tails um heads for chest tails
for legs it's going to land on Tails hey
Siri flip a coin tail Tails Tails I told
you [__] all right I'm ready
[Music]
[Applause]
all right you either do this or you're
blowing that count it's lightwe
[Music]
that was heavy as [__] I can't even lie
that's just light work that's light work
right you don't work out like me bro
yeah I your him your himothy of course
all right look at my size compared to
you what are you going to say when I do
this that's that's just me warming
up what you doing right
[Music]
did we hit the go yet you have to make
an appointment to talk to me
son by the way I don't drink water from
this I just ran out of a container to
mix my electrolytes and [__] like [__]
dude we almost blew the account earlier
and now we have surpassed the goal for
the week if you guys look at this on the
daily time frame you guys can see how we
body closed under that line exact how I
had explained so this [__] can easily
easily easily come down here which that
would pretty much put us in a position
of about $6 to $7,000 in profit of this
so once again I've surpassed the goal
for the week in the first trade look at
my Instagram bro my Instagram is blowing
up 100,000 people looking at my stories
every single
day I'm I come over here and then we can
see look at this look how many these are
all like new people look at this guy
eating some [__] potato
or whatever corn look at this all these
people are catching the traes sup my
guy this guy did the light skin face bro
this guy up
$1,000 on the USD JPY trades that we
caught and the USD CHF I don't care what
anyone has to say FX at she does the
best go check out that guy's Instagram
my boy
Mike turning
[Laughter]
$100 bro it's all day like I get
hundreds of you guys every single
day so we fasted made people money we
made money uh hit the gym play
basketball what is there to do bro what
else do we
do
K Godfather theme song
I'm himothy the point is that we are up
$8,000 on the challenge right now by
simply set and forgetting the goal for
the week was $6,000 we are now $22,000
above that you guys can see right here
on both phones both exactly the same and
then you guys can clearly see right here
on the charts exactly what I was
explaining earlier so we originally
wanted to enter at the break and retest
of this and we did not then we did enter
up here but this shows you guys how
these zones that I spot out every single
Sunday with my students are so accurate
because we did end up break and
retesting this point to then continue
heading to the downside we could have
literally added a position right at this
point here to continue the sells to the
downside obviously we're not going to do
that cuz it's a highrisk trade but we're
literally halfway to our takeprofit and
we already way above the profit Target
that we wanted to go but I do believe
this could easily head all the way to
down here very soon so all I plan to do
right now is simply set and forget the
daily time frame looks absolutely
beautiful 4H hour time for because it
closed under that line exactly how I
explained we came back we retested that
line 4H hour is looking absolutely solid
it's perfect GJ on the other hand
completely wrong avoided this loss to
Perfection Euro USD obviously we have
the big head and shoulders the move
happened that's gone and then GBP CAD
right now we are literally still waiting
on this break and retest to then sell so
for now all we have to do is just let
usdchf right set and forget it is
currently it is currently what time is
it
811 p.m. Tuesday afternoon so if we
close I got around $8 $9,000 in profit
probably this same week I'll try and
flip it to then 20,000 this same week
moving quick boys moving quick all right
what is up guys trade out there right
now it's
about
1:25 in the morning 1:30 in the morning
um technically
Wednesday yeah Wednesday night Wednesday
morning potato
potato I'm tired of [__]
but I don't get tired of looking at
these [__] profits so check
this out so Seas is knocked out so I'm
kind of holding the camera right now and
this is just showing you guys the power
of set and forget you know what's funny
I saw 10,000 in profit in the p&l so let
me show you guys all right so bear with
me guys I'm working this big ass camera
and I don't know how to use it so right
now we are currently floating about
$6,000 in profit the account is
currently at $99,000 in equity and you
guys can see this trade right here is
literally continuing the momentum to the
downside just continuing the set and
forget Trend that's why you got to trade
with the trend the trend is your friend
so you guys can see the for close very
strong I am going to just continue to
hold this trade uh if tomorrow closes
under this line right here not this one
I'm just copy and pasting if the
Candlestick closes under this line right
there we will probably turn this into
over
$115,000 easily so let wait for now
simply just set and forget so GBP JPY
ass Euro USD ass GBP CAD ass only
focusing on one pair right now so yeah
we're to check back in tomorrow just to
show you guys once again what time is it
right now 1127 in the morning Miami time
[Music]
[__] with the sudden forget strategy
[__] I literally went to sleep last
night like at 2:30 in the morning and I
saw like about I don't know like in the
account like $7,000 in profit like you
know what it's just s and forget I woke
up at 8:30 I literally did
this oh and I just ran straight here
right now market update 9:00 in the
morning we are up
$14,000 on the account bro this is
[__] crazy look at this [__]
literally exactly what I explained last
night if price ended up closing under
this line we're simply going to continue
to set and forget if you notice my
overall take profit hits exactly where
we've been anticipating 4H hour
absolutely beautiful all of these
structure points have been used as break
and retest points to then continue the
sells to the downside this trade has
been
absolutely phenomenal look at this this
trade can easily I'm talking about
easily make it to this line right here
which is going to be this next structure
point right here so currently right now
this is [__]
$114,000 bro $100 to $14,000 in 3 weeks
or two weeks and a half if you have not
subscribed and you haven't joined the S
forget community link below you're
missing out by the way this is real
[__] she was 5 grand this [__]
[Music]
goldplated it's empty suck about to shot
something through the roof yeah this is
real so I'm feeling like that guy today
you know what I'm saying I got that
thing on me I got that thing on me I
don't know bro I'm hyped that's it so
basically what I'm going to do is right
now we're going to literally close in
the next 15 probably 30 minutes um cuz
right now let's see that we body Clos
under this is exactly what so we did not
body close under that right there which
is not good we wanted a body Clos under
that line cuz if it did then we'll
literally make it to them this line
that's just how it works I just know
I'm just I'm just that I'm himothy I'm
just that guy you know so since we did
not close into that now we're going to
have a rejection exactly how we've done
here reject to the upsite so we got to
get out before we before we miss out on
all the profits so GBP
JPY uh currently this trade was just a
complete
violation Euro USD looks like it's
pulling back GBP CAD look yeah this is
prob yeah this is probably going to be
our next trade yeah this can be the next
trade that can then take us to like 30
40,000 just waiting on this trade to
then do this to then enter the sell to
the downside yeah that's pretty much it
sat up for ladies and gentlemen today
we're probably going to go hit the gym
and uh see what other missions kind of
pop up throughout the day so once again
just to show you guys where we are up
the
$4,000 oh wait this one's updated give
it a second you see it oh there you go
updated all right market update is
literally 30 minutes later we are still
in the trade so now we're up
15,500 so exactly what I was mentioning
to you guys earlier I have to see like
you can't just close a trade right away
right because you got to look so
obviously we're going to close a trade
because we wanted it to close under this
line well under this right here and
actively looks like we are piercing
through that so this Candlestick closes
in the next 5 minutes as you can see
right over here and if this Candlestick
closes under this line it will mean that
it closes under this structure point and
then there I truly do believe that it
could then easily go from here to then
this point right here so right now we
literally got to wait the next 5 minutes
if it closes above like that I'm going
to close it right then and there if not
I'll squeeze it in for the little bit
extra right here just to show you guys
we're up about
15,100 right now [__]
bro Trace set are reversing on me dude
look at this Bro [__] Trace set
reversing we were up like 15,000 here
and
now like I said I forget too much
bro it's like we closed the trade like 2
hours ago so right now it's currently
12:30 in the afternoon right here you
guys can see where the account is it's
officially closed at
$115,000 you guys can see right here in
the history so you guys can see that we
officially closed this trade at
$122,200 in profit so we we closed it
earlier literally as soon as I told you
guys pretty much after it closed that
line so it did make it all the way up to
this structure point and then it had a
reaction so pretty much exactly what I
explained it's going to have a reaction
from that structure point right here and
if we follow this line it's exactly what
it did so our entry points are as
precise as they get our stop losses our
take profit everything with the seven
fre strategy [__] sniper yo the goal
for the week was 6 grand we are at5 ,000
so if we were to close at 6 grand this
week the goal for next week was to turn
6 to 12 so we just did this week and
next week's goal oh [__] we should go on
a
vacation right ahead of schedule we
should just [__] off for two weeks right
yeah I think we shouldn't we should stop
doing content for two weeks since we're
caught up that's what I'm saying and we
should just stop cuz you're not
subscribed to the channel right now so
you don't want to watch this series so
hit the Subscribe button and you know
what I feel like I feel like when I'm
into the trades for so long I just
become numb to it and I obviously like
I've done like a thousand Instagram
stories already about it so I'm kind of
like numb to what we just did right now
like
$155,000 is insane what we're going to
do now is see if we can turn this5 to
$30,000 this week because there's great
opportunities if there's great
opportunities there's no reason for me
to stop trading all I have to do is just
wait for those great opportunities so
trade up there on the other markets so
GBP
JPY no entry no trade here here your USD
pullback no trade no entry GBP cat so
this is our next victim right here left
head right shoulder so we are finally
having this break that we have been
anticipating now all we got to wait for
is that retest and then we will enter
this trade as a sell to then the
downside so GBP CAD is looking very
interesting the daily time frame is
finally having that bearish break we
need the retest to then sell so it looks
very very very solid now pretty much it
is currently
1235 in the afternoon we're going to go
do a set forget commercial right now
we're going to go do some donuts in the
Ferrari dropping a one time merch real
quick so yeah just do some donuts proba
eat gym and let's see where the day
takes us really excited to see how your
energy is going to be when we reach 300K
I think my energy is going to be a lot
better I think it's going to be a lot
better so we just closed out the trade
15,00 $ in profit so we're doing a
commercial right now for set and forget
merch these are like basic very basic
t-shirts t-shirts do like one time drops
they sell out and then we never sell
them again cuz look this gray matches
perfectly with the Gage it's almost as
identical color that you're going to get
so you know we got the GoPro ready and
we're just going to hit some donuts for
a little ad that we're going to do
for s
[Music]
oh
all right so it's been like 2 and 1/2
months just woke over man na I fell
asleep outside tanning my Phantom is
fat bro I've had this car for 2 and 1/2
months half of its life has been on a
tow truck like with these cars it's a
hit or miss you get a really really
really good good one or you get one like
mine that just [__] [__] up and I'm
paying $6,000 a month for this and I've
driven it three times in two months
[Music]
all right guys trade update So currently
it is
11:51 p.m. so right now we are literally
exactly at the same spot $15,000 in
profit we have not taken another trade
so it's a little late it's about to be
midnight but you know got to pull up to
Jordan's house he just bought a cold
plunge so we're going to pretty much set
it up for him he can't set it up himself
right now and we're going to just let
Jordan show a little bit of his story
and how he plans to recover and yeah
tomorrow we didn't hit the gym today
either so tomorrow we're going to work
double make up for that so let's go help
Jordan get this cop PL set up so it's
going to help him with the inflammation
so let's do it
[Music]
let's go this is it yeah it looks way
smaller here I mean the reviews look
decent but I guess this just like pops
up yeah I think it's like one of these
popping up ones yeah we're going to set
up this cold plunge going to help
Jordan's inflammation with his legs tell
you guys a little bit about his story
and what he's going through how he plans
to get better story is really motivated
so show you guys to not make any [__]
excuses all right what's going on
everyone so in Alex's last YouTube video
I was going through the comments and a
lot of people wanted to know my story
and we're curious as to like what
happened to me and why I was in a
wheelchair so I'm real quick I'm going
just break it down to you guys and give
you guys like a little summary of like
my story so pretty much like two years
two and a half years ago I got um
diagnosed with cancer and I had to do
like chemo uh radiation therapy like the
whole nine yards and then I was good for
sometime I was good for like eight
months I was able to like focus on my
trading I thanks to Alex and his
mentorship like I literally was able to
take my trading to the next level and
then after that when I took my trading
to the next Next Level I got hit with
like the cancer again I had to literally
focus on that again so pretty much I had
to do chemo radiation therapy all over
again so pretty much two full cycles of
that and then after that thank God thank
Alex we got back on track on our trading
we were killing it and then we got hit
with the cancer again so now we're
literally dealing with that again now
but what's different from the approach
I'm going to take now as to the approach
that we took last time is that now I'm
going to take like a more holistic route
and I'm going to go to like a a
different doctor cuz here in the US the
doctor and everything is like a little
bit like shady so outside the US I'm
going to see if I could find like
something that's going to help me a
little bit better now I remember when I
was trying to become like a profitable
Trader I used to see like certain things
that would affect me and my outside
circumstances and I used to be like crap
like why am I going through this or like
I used to like let it get me down right
but the point is it doesn't matter what
you're going through like you could use
me as an example if I don't let this get
me down you shouldn't let anything let
you down for example if you're going
through like a tough money situation
which is like very common and trust me
I've been broke as well too like I know
what it's like to be completely broke
I'm telling you like it's not permanent
like you're going to once you get out of
the situation you're going to be
grateful to be in that situation if that
makes sense so like for you to
appreciate going fast you got to know
what it's like to go slow if you're
going through a tough spot right now
just know that it's not your permanent
situation and it's your mindset about
the situation that matters now it's
pretty crazy right cuz like I've been
trading for 6 years so I spent like 6
years working toward a specific goal and
like once you reach that goal it's crazy
cuz like you hit the goal but you get
something else taken away so like going
through this whole perspective has a
affected me in the sense of like I've
reached like some very personal goals
that I wanted to reach but I don't have
like the things that I used to once
value at a certain time when I didn't
have those goals met so it's it's a
literally like a crazy balance in life
that just makes you realize that like it
makes you realize that the materialistic
things and everything that we Chase is
obviously nice but you have to be in
check and your health has to be on point
because without that like there's
literally nothing so it's pretty crazy I
would say this is affected me in the
sense of like um just being more
grateful for everything and honestly
like like just appreciate everything
more and when I'm out of this situation
like I'm definitely going to enjoy just
living my normal life again like a
normal routine driving my car yeah I
would say it's whole situations just
made me realize like that the small
things that we take in life for granted
are really the big things and you just
got to be grateful for everything that's
going on in your life even though if
it's a tough situation I promise you
when you get out of it you'll be
grateful that you went through it so I
plan on getting out of this situation by
eating definitely eating a lot more
Health like just cutting out a lot of
the crap so no more sugar I feel sugar
is like the number one cause for cancer
it's crazy how the doctors here give you
sugar and then other people will tell
you not see sugar but definitely cut
back on sugar going cut back on sugar
I'm going to be doing some immune
therapy which is something here in the
states that's that's legal but um I'm
going to be doing something out of state
that's not legal here so we're going to
see how that goes so it's crazy cuz the
first time I got diagnosed with cancer I
was doing like really good in trading
and then I just went to complete crap
like literally as soon as I got
diagnosed with cancer and I was going
through chemo I went to like a 3 four
month losing streak and then I didn't
get get out of that losing streak until
I stopped doing chemotherapy but what's
crazy is now 2 years later I did
chemotherapy and I was on a 23 week
winning streak so it literally did not
affect me at all it just it just goes to
show the growth like in the mindset and
pretty much just the growth in two years
of play in treading yeah just know
anything that you guys set your mind to
you could achieve no one could stop you
by yourself and your mindset is the most
powerful thing that you have so I leave
you guys with that it need a
p and and
uh we just put a bucket in it look oh we
just put a bucket in it right now so
this bucket is going to pretty much let
him sit kind of high we're going to go
get ice and be right
back all right we got eight bags of ice
bro this is going to
suck what do you think are you
ready see I'm
first more
all right guys trade update we got
literally no sleep yesterday after
Jordan after look let me just show you
guys my sleep look at this yesterday we
got 22% recovery so we fell like 4 hours
of sleep we fell asleep at 3:00 in the
morning and we woke up at 7:30 in the
morning you might be asking but Alex you
left Jordan's house like at 1:20 in the
morning why' you fall asleep at 3: well
you know took another trade you know
what I'm saying well not not one of
these trades right the account's exactly
the same we took another trade you know
what I'm saying when you win a trade
right you turn $100 to
15,000 you know you get some
opportunities out there and
um you got to take it when the
opportunity is there you got to take it
you think I wanted to do that SN no but
I'm a soldier all right long story short
account let me show you guys my effects
look but before that actually let me
show you guys the the trade so look the
trade right now obviously continue to go
I could have literally kept holding this
trade right now we'd probably be easily
at around 18 19,000 just shows you guys
once you trade with the trend all you
got to do is [__] set and forget so
this trade
completely perfectly played out trade
next GJ GJ telling you we were wrong we
were wrong literally forever EUR us
looks like it came back to add another
entry after this left head uh left head
right shoulder and then we retest so it
looks like it's continuing to the
downside but now this trade right here
now last night as I was um entering
other
markets and um using proper risk
management I wasn't paying attention to
these markets last night and we missed
out on a on another trade so this trade
right here gvp CAD literally exactly how
I explained this so we had the left head
and the right shoulder we had the break
exactly how I wanted to we had the
retest exactly how I wanted to and then
look at that the move ended up happening
last night this is pretty much the entry
right here so this was a trade that I
ended up missing out it is what it is uh
honestly I don't really care I'm not
super greedy I'm not really I'm not
worried about it you know because we're
definitely ahead of schedule currently
right now let me show you guys the my
effects account before that what time is
it it is 8:30 in the morning right so I
keep forgetting this so let's look right
here so look at the time so if I refresh
the time it is 8:29 8:30 in the morning
I don't know why it does that but so let
me actually sign in right now to the my
effect book so I can show you guys so as
you guys can see here on the my effect
book just hid in the broker cuz I don't
promote Brokers so this is the my effect
book on the 100 know as you guys can see
I'm hiding the broker name cuz I don't
promote Brokers right now you guys can
see the current balance show them that
Equity chart like show them the chart of
that market right there look at that
[__] that [__] looks like a [__]
rocket ship down here you guys can see
literally all of the Pips that we have
gotten you guys can see our
profitability it's 100% profitability
because we haven't lost a trade if you
would have lost a trade would have blown
the account we've taken five trades as
of right now every single trade we've
taken is a short um our best trade is
$8,000 our best trade is 200 Pips uh
pretty much everything is pretty cool so
yeah now we're going what what are we
going to do now we're going to go drift
the Ferrari for no reason no we did that
yesterday today's another day we just do
it again yeah we can enter a new
position now so since we technically
missed this High entry right here this
could be down the next retest of this
really ugly left head right shoulder so
if I were to draw it out like this it'd
be a little ugly but you you know it's
like it's like last night's trade like
had to do what I had to do you know it
was hey it was a profitable trade I'll
tell you that any trade that you take
and you execute and you come out
successful on the other side that's a
profitable trade remember that trade of
[__] not everybody will understand all
right so now this trade right here we're
having a pull back to what looks to be
like this neckline right here now here
is where I'm going to be interested in
entering this position this is what the
1 hour is looking like so we're back at
this area of Interest level of support
level of support now we got a level of
support right here and we got to reject
this if we reject it give you my entry
signal I will then enter this trade
right around here so let's just be
patient on this trade and I'll update
you guys so see you guys throughout the
day when a trade
knocks take that jum dude trade
update
9:23 in the morning all right what is it
an hour later look at this [__] exactly
what the [__] I just explained literally
retest this level to then look for the
new entry to sell bro this is [__]
crazy if you are not subscribed and you
have not joined the ctif community
you're missing
[Music]
out I bet you guys don't know how the
[__] to cut a watermelon well neither do
I you guys are here watching this video
how to turn on you know $100 into a
million you guys are learning how to do
that well I know how to do that it's
easy I don't know how to cut a
watermelon so I have to watch a YouTube
video on how to cut a watermelon but I
don't have to watch a YouTube video how
to turn $100 to a mil you know so we're
going to cut this now for the car wash
guys are outside and some food I don't
have a cutting board so don't roast my
cutting board right now and we're just
going to give some of these watermelons
to the guys cuz they're washing the cars
really hot day I at me right now we got
to get back have you ever had watermelon
with lime try that
what kind of [__] is
[Applause]
[Music]
that it's a full bite how was it it's
pretty good it gives a really good taste
right it's like sweet and sour at the
same
yo I have a competition for you guys all
right say all right sh luck whoever eats
the watermelon the fastest
wins all this money right here
$500 all right so all you have to do is
eat it like this how I have just eaten
it right here completely to the end okay
all right deal right here all right yeah
fine yeah just make a mess whatever wait
what all right ready three two 1
[Music]
go oh my God look at the floor
dude C Ladi are in an hour I know all
right well you know what the good thing
is that give me the M
thing to the rim like I have I have to
see a
white if you guys ever put lime on
watermelon it tastes great let try look
try try try try try BR look I do it all
the
time it doesn't no it doesn't leave me
yo so it it's honestly in between you
guys
I'm not going to lie my nose was
stopping
me
m all right all right now just be
careful you guys are going to step what
do I get for second place nothing you
mean second place second place is the
first loser you get nothing that's why
you never [__] say yo
today day what time is it let me get
your phone all right trade update right
now 710 in the afternoon we are not
trading right now it's what day is it
today Thursday Thursday Thursday 70 in
the afternoon we're going to play some
basketball right now ball up
[Music]
it's it's all right but when you get all
right guys so market update it is
currently
12:18 in the afternoon we got to haircut
every single Friday you got to look
fresh for the weekend for the weekend
trades you know what I'm saying come on
we take a trade earlier this week come
on you guys get the [__] program all
right so this week we're actually out of
the four markets that we were interested
in trading at the beginning of the week
two of them played out one of them
didn't play out at all and then one of
them was a loss if you would have taken
every single trade or been interested of
taking every single trade even if you
would have taken two of the wins and two
of the losses you would still be up
because of the risk to reward so let me
explain so first things first is going
to be GBP JPY so GBP JPY you can see at
the beginning of the week we're waiting
for price to have a pull back into this
area to then sell because we're going to
have the left head and then the right
shoulder to retest the EMA this
resistance resistance level to that and
sell obviously we were interested in the
buys to get to that point but the buys
never presented themselves so we never
took that byy but you guys can see how
this sell of the overall Market which is
the real trade actually ended up playing
out massively this is a massive move
right here this trade right here alone
if you would have taken it right around
here would have given you 1,000 Pips
which is [__] insane for that to
happen in one single week so this is GBP
JPY this trade did not give us an
opportunity so out of the four markets
this is the one that did not give it to
us and if you did take it it would be a
loss next is going to be obviously USD
CHF you guys already know at the
beginning of the week we were up here we
had major moves to the downside guys
this is literally been one of the
[__] craziest moves I have seen in a
very long time we close our trade out
over here for a total of a one to4 risk
to reward and at the time that was a lot
but if I just continued to set and
forget and I would have continued to
hold this trade all the way down here we
would have a 1 to 15 meaning that this
$115,000 that we have right now in the
account would easily be at 30 no no what
the it be like at $60 $70,000 probably
even more Hest almost like 100,000 cuz
we 10x it so obviously that didn't
happen we got out here so this is
obviously a win next is Euro USD so EUR
USD was the first trade that played out
to Perfection we have the left head
right shoulder read this the neckline
sell this trade would give us a one to
two so this played out perfectly and
then last but not least is GBP CAD so
GBP CAD is just giving us the entry
right now on this market we've
officially had the break and now we're
having the r the retest that we're
looking to enter this market so this is
the trade that just simply did not give
us the opportunity to enter the trade to
the downside so those are the four
markets that we are we're interested at
trading at the beginning of the week
definitely a profitable week and this is
what we do every single Sunday with my
students I literally share with my
students every single one of these
trades that I'm taking on the 100 to the
mail account on Sunday swings if you
guys click the link below you guys are
going to know what set and forget is
truly and how you can get access to
these same markets with me every single
Sunday because I get on a call with the
students and I break down all of these
markets right here so every single one
of these markets that you see here I get
on a call with them and I break down
every single one of these markets and
out of every single one of those markets
I find the top two top three top four
best opportunities that the market has
to give because if you only Trade One
Market you're just limiting yourself to
just one type of trading at that very
time there's been markets in this watch
list right here like literally in this
watch list I don't remember the last
time I traded GBP and ZD like I could
have not traded that pair for 8 months
but there could be an opportunity next
month where it gives it to to me so if
you only trade gbpnzd kind of just
cutting yourself short to only trading
the opportunities that that market gives
you which might not be the best so I
have many different markets because I
look for the best ones that's going to
do every single Sunday with my students
where I'm going to be sharing with them
the trades that I take on this 100 to
the mail account so if you want to join
and be part of those calls click the
link in the description below we get on
a call every single Sunday you join the
Discord you guys will get access to me
directly ask me questions live so with
that being said click the link below
I'll see you guys inside the S foret
Community appreciate you guys watching
this video all the way to the end and
make sure you guys hit that like And
subscribe button and I'll see you guys
next week for another 100 to the mill
Series where we're going to try and take
$155,000 to
$30,000 see you guys next week